本字幕由夜桜字幕组制作
翻译:お兄様
Oh, you two will be so much fun.
你俩玩得肯定很开心啊
时轴:ELF
That's enough!
泥垢了
Tristan...?
崔斯坦？
压制:雪夜
What's going on?
发生啥了
Sophia! Are you alright?
索菲亚，你没事吧
- I...
我。。。
- Are you hurt, or...
你受伤了吗？
I'm alright.
我没事
What did she do to you?!
她对你做什么了
Surely you're not this dense, Prince.
待会儿你就没这么淡定了
Shut... up.
闭····嘴
Sophia, listen to me. I...
索菲亚····听我说
I saw...
我看见·····
Everything.
所有事
She saw it all, Prince.
她都看见了，王子（大猪蹄子和这女的偷情吧 推测剧情这女的喜欢索菲亚然后使了个诡计 明白？
What do you have to say for yourself?
你还有什么好辩解的
Shouldn't you be on your knees?
你不该跪下么
Why, you...
为什么，你这个····
We've had enough of you for one night,
Prince.
我们受够你了
Tristan!
崔斯特！！
Don't worry about him, Duchess.
别担心他，女爵
I'll entertain you.
我来愉悦你
What-
什么？
What are you doing?
你在干嘛
Where is Tristan?
崔斯特在哪
Back at the castle...
传送回城堡了
...so we can have some fun.
这样我们就能玩玩了
How do you like to play?
你想怎么玩
I....
我···
I'm sorry...
对不起
I didn't mean to...
我不是故意····（和崔斯特好的
Is this how you like to play?
你就想这么玩？
What kind of an abomination are you?
你是何方妖孽
That's no way to speak to your new lover,
Sophia.
这可不是你该和新欢说话的方式呀，索菲亚
Any last words?
遗言？
What's that, Duchess?你这什么意思？女爵
At a loss for words?
都说不出话了？
Stop whining and put your arms behind your
back...
别哀怨了，把手放到身后
and keep them there.
把手背好
That's a good girl. Show me how much you
want my cock.
好姑娘，让我看看你有多想要我的X（字幕君很害羞的 你们自行体会
take it
接好了
There's no need to pretend anymore. We
both know you love getting face fucked.
别装了，我们都知道你喜欢被口
Oh Duchess, you're so good at sucking my
cock.
哦，女爵，你可真擅长吸我的X
But now it's time for the real test.
但是好戏现在才开始
Look at you... such an eager slut.
看看你自己，饥渴的荡妇
Can you feel how hard you've made me?
你能感觉你让我多硬成什么样了吗
I'm so fucking hard it aches...
硬的疼
And it's all your fault, Sophia.
这是你的错，索菲亚
So now you're going to have to take every
last inch of this cock...
现在你要吃下每一寸X
'til your lips... are here.
嘴唇放这儿
Understand?
明白？
Good.
好的
This won't be easy for you... but we
know that's how you like it, right?
对你来说有点难，不过我们都知道你喜欢对吗？
Now...
现在
Open your mouth.
张嘴
That's it, Sophia. Deeper.
就这样，索菲亚，深一点
Almost there... just a little more...
快到了，再深一点点
Yes... keep going.
继续
Just... a little deeper.
再深一点
Yes!
对
Oh... look at you.
哦 看看你
You swallowed a whole cock.
你把整个X都吞了
Now as a treat, I'm going to throat fuck
you 'til I come.
作为奖励，我要深喉然后射进去
Wake up, Sophia...
醒醒，索菲亚
We're not done yet.
还没完
My cock wants a taste of that pussy.
我的X想尝尝你的X
What?
什么？
Your cock is hard again?
你又硬了？
What do you take me for? Your Prince?
你当我是谁？你的王子？（崔斯特 那么没用
Now... let's see how tight you are.
让我们来瞧瞧你多紧
Your cock feels so good...
你的X好舒服呀
I need your cock inside of me.
我要你的X进入我
So desperate for my cock... I'm going to fuck you senseless.
这么饥渴，我要X得你麻木
You came inside of me?
你射进去了？
There's so much cum in my pussy...
好多好多精液呀
I've never had this much cum inside of me...
从没有过这么多精液
There's barely any cum in you. That's
just one load.
没多少啊，才一发
Yes, but... Tristan isn't allowed to come
in my pussy until I'm Queen.
是的，但是我不让崔斯特射在里面除非我当了王后
He's not allowed in my, uh...
也不准他爆···
Just say it, Duchess, and I will.
说出来呀，女爵
What are you talking about?
你在说什么呀（我不懂呀
Alright then... beg me.
好啊，求我
Beg you? I don't beg.
求你？我不求人
Beg me to fuck you in the ass.
求我X你的菊花
What?! I would never!
！！！我绝不会
Stop lying already, Sophia.
别骗自己了，索菲亚
We both know you want me to fuck you in
the ass, so beg.
我们都知道你想让我爆菊
Fuck me. Fuck me in the ass.
爆我菊吧····(OMG
Beg me!
求！！！我！！！
Please... Please fuck me. Please fuck my ass.
求求你 求求你 爆我的菊吧
Well, if you insist.
好吧，你求我的话
Your ass is too tight.
你的菊好紧
I'm sorry. I guess we'll have to do this another time.
抱歉，我看我们得下次做了
That's better.
现在好多了
Now that your ass has had a taste of my
cock, let's have some real fun.
好，现在你的菊尝到了我的X，我们好好玩玩
Close your eyes.
闭眼
What is this!?
怎么回事
How do you like the view?
这儿风景如何
Now, spread your ass.
菊花张开
How is it you can change like that?
你怎么变成那样的
With magic, of course.
魔法咯····
I wish I could do that... make me like you!
我希望我也能那样，把我变成那样
A vampire?
变成吸血鬼？
No, like you were before... just now.
不，是那样呀（你真坏
Very well.
好呀
Ready for more, Duchess?
准备好了吗，女爵
Are you, Cerene?你是，赛伦。